ggl.com 2007-12-25

# GGL - Privacy

## PRIVACY POLICY

**Overview**

Professional Interactive Entertainment (PIE) (together with its subsidiaries, "GGL" or "ClanBase.com" or "we") considers the protection of personal privacy to be one of our most important values. This privacy policy ("Policy") gives you specific information on how we protect your privacy, how we treat personal information, and the choices you have. This privacy policy complies with the Safe Harbor framework under the E.U. Data Protection Directive. In addition, PIE self-certifies compliance with the Safe Harbor framework to the U.S. Department of Commerce.

This Policy applies to all web sites and services owned or provided by PIE and its divisions (including GGL.com & Clanbase.com), which we refer to here collectively as "PIE Sites". PIE Sites include, but are not limited to Clanbase.com, iTG.com, as well as other GGL services. From time to time we may add new sites, domain names or services to those listed above. Please note that this Policy applies only to sites owned and services maintained by PIE or its corporate subsidiaries and not to web sites or services provided by other companies or organizations to which we link.

As a condition of using the PIE Sites, you agree to be bound by the terms of this Policy. Additional terms and conditions, which govern your use of the PIE Sites are contained in our Terms & Conditions, and, as applicable, in certain other service-specific license agreements, which you will be notified of at the time of your registration for the applicable services.

The Policy is accessible through the GGL Sites in several ways, including from a link entitled "Privacy Policy" at the bottom of the GGL.com home page. You acknowledge that this Policy may change over time. If we make a material change to the terms of this Policy, we will give you 30 days notice of those changes ("Notice Period") through reasonably prominent disclosure, including via email. However, you should check the PIE Sites (and GGL.com in particular) regularly for these and other important announcements. Your continued use of the PIE Sites following the Notice Period will signify that you agree to these changes.

**Children**

The PIE Sites are not directed to children under the age of 13. The PIE Sites prohibit registration by, and PIE will not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from, anyone under 13. This requirement will be posted at points of data collection within the PIE Sites, such as registration for services.

Note to Parents: If you have any concerns about the PIE Sites, please contact us via our online forums. PIE encourages parents to spend time online with their children. We also urge parents to instruct their children never to give out their real names, addresses or phone numbers without parental permission when using the Internet.

**Information Collection, Storage and Use**

We refer to information that identifies an individual as "Personal Information." In general, PIE collects Personal Information from users of the PIE Sites in connection with access to certain online areas or services, including during (i) registration for certain online community services and tools such as message boards, chat rooms or other community services; (ii) registration for special communications, such as email updates and newsletters; (iii) subscription registration; (iv) user surveys; (v) events, sweepstakes, contests or promotions; and (vi) registration for online multi- or single-player gaming, either through the PIE Sites, within a game publisher's site or through the game itself. Your Personal Information is stored on PIE computer servers (or those of its service providers).

Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information in public areas of a PIE Site, such as the member home pages and message boards, your information can be viewed and possibly used by others. We advise users to be especially careful in such public areas about disclosing Personal Information, such as full name, home address, or phone number.

Below are more details about the Personal Information we gather and how we, or our agents may use those. Additionally, if you decide to subscribe to Services offered by Third Parties, your information or partial information may be disclosed to that service provider to enable him to fulfill its business.

**A. Email Newsletters:** PIE offers email newsletters to its registered users. We will use your email address to send you only the specific newsletter(s) that you have signed up for. If you want to update your email address or stop receiving a newsletter, follow the procedures to unsubscribe at the bottom of any newsletter we send you or simply visit http://ggl.com to update your personal profile.

**B. Membership Information:** Currently PIE collects the following personal information: First Name, Last Name, Birthday, City, State, ZIP, Country, Email and Gender.  
We may also ask for additional information about you and your interests. We do this so we can better understand your preferences and tailor the PIE Sites to suit you better. The more information you volunteer, the more we can tailor the PIE Sites and promotions to your interests. Additionally, third-party service providers may require you to assent to their privacy party as a condition to receiving their service.

* Service Providers: We may offer our members other services provided by third parties such as email and user-pages, among others. When you register for a membership on a PIE Site or activate a related service by clicking on a particular service link (i.e. email) on a PIE Site, you may be automatically registered to receive the services we offer and some of your Personal Information may be transferred from PIE to those third-party service providers. By becoming a member to such services, you authorize us and our third-party service providers to send you email updates and information about promotions and special offers. We take care to require that our third-party service providers only use our member's data as necessary to provide the particular service and to give you updates on that service provider's products and services.

* Game Owners/Publishers/Technology Providers: We provide game owners/publishers with certain hosted technology and software that enables various game related functionalities, such as online multi- or single-player gaming. If you are not already a registered user of the PIE Sites you may be asked to provide Personal Information in connection with your use of such services. We may share Personal Information with game owners/publishers/technology providers that offer such services to enable those entities to operate the services you have elected to receive. Game owners/publishers/technology providers may also use Personal Information for other business purposes, provided that such use shall be in compliance with the terms of this Policy, except that a game owner/publisher/technology providers will not contact you or otherwise, use or transfer your Personal Information, unless you have expressly consented. Upon giving such consent your Personal Information will be subject to the game owner's/publisher's/technology provider's privacy policy.

**C. Email Updates to Members:** We may contact you regarding account status, changes to this Policy, our User Agreement or other terms of use, to confirm your registration or for any other business reason related to your use of PIE Sites.

**D. Promotions:** We may ask you for Personal Information at other times, including, but not limited to, when you enter sweepstakes, contests or promotions sponsored by PIE or a third party. If you choose to enter sweepstakes, contests or promotions sponsored by a third party, the Personal Information you provide will be subject to the privacy policy of the third party sponsor. We encourage you to check the applicable third party policy before providing any Personal Information.

**E. Surveys and User Research:** PIE may conduct email and web-delivered surveys from time to time, as well as instant polls, to gather information about our users. Taking these surveys and polls is entirely optional. You have no obligation to respond to them. We share only the aggregate results of these surveys, not Personal Information, with our advertisers and partners to help them better understand our services and monitor the reach of their advertising or other offerings on our service. We also use some of the Personal Information that you provide in these surveys to help us understand your interests and to make the PIE Sites more useful to you.

**F. Use of Cookies:** On the Internet, a "cookie" is a piece of information (a file) that a Web site transfers to a user's computer for record-keeping purposes. The use of cookies is common on the Internet. The process we use to serve advertisements and to track use of the PIE Sites involves cookies. We use cookies to recognize users who have already registered for an PIE Site, allowing those users to speed up their future activities on the PIE Sites. Cookies help PIE and our advertising service (discussed below) track the frequency and placement of advertisements. Cookies also enable us to measure aggregate (total) usage and traffic to the PIE Sites and to specific offerings. This aids us in producing content that best meets our users' preferences. In order to implement new services, we may use other types of cookies as well. We also may use cookies to understand better what parts of the PIE Sites you like best. We may use that information to display advertisements that we think will be of particular interest to you. You may configure your browser to reject cookies, but this may interfere with some functionality of the PIE Sites. Certain pages of the PIE Sites may contain electronic images (called a "single-pixel GIF") that allow a web site to count users who have visited that page. PIE occasionally uses web beacons on the PIE Sites in order to count users and to recognize registered users by accessing the PIE cookies.

**G. Purchase of Products or Services:** When you purchase products or services from or through the PIE Sites we may require Personal Information such as name, address, telephone number and billing information, including credit card, debit card or bank account data. PIE will not disclose your Personal Information, including billing information, except to the extent necessary to complete your transaction, for example during an online purchase or where needed to deliver a product or service you ordered.

**H. Software Updates; Interactive Material:** PIE automatically updates software used in conjunction with certain of the services available on the PIE Sites. In order to update this software, PIE collects a user's current version information from the user's computer. This information is not archived and is only used to determine which software requires updating. 

**I. Sites You Visit:** As you access our Partner Sites and browse around the PIE Sites, PIE may store information about which pages and which Partner Sites you visit and other information presented in your browser's URL address line. PIE will use this information to help determine what our users are most interested in.

**J. Sharing Non-Personal Information:** PIE may share information that is not Personal Information -- meaning non-personal, aggregate, or summary, information regarding our users -- with other third parties not mentioned in this Policy. This kind of information does not identify you individually.

**K. Merger or Acquisition:** In the event of a merger, acquisition, reorganization, sale of all or substantially all of its assets, or the sale of an individual website owned by PIE, PIE may transfer your Personal Information to a third party as a part of such merger, acquisition, reorganization, or sale.

**L. Legal Authorities:** We may also disclose Personal Information in cases when we reasonably believe that it is necessary to identify someone who may be violating PIE policies or PIE Sites" User Agreements or other terms of use, or who may be a threat to PIE or third party rights, property, or personal safety. The PIE Sites may disclose Personal Information to comply with valid legal process such as a duly issued search warrant, subpoena or court order.

**Access to Other Sites through PIE**

**Our Partner Sites:** You should be aware that when you are on a PIE Site, you will have the opportunity to visit, or link to, other sites associated with PIE. These sites are identified as our "Partner Sites". These sites are not owned or operated by PIE, but are part of a larger network of sites with which the PIE Sites share content and advertising opportunities. We do not share your Personal Information with these Partner Sites, except as noted above.

**Linking to Other Sites:** You may also visit independent web sites, not owned or operated by PIE, through links on the PIE Sites. Such sites are operated by external, third-party service providers. Some of these sites will have their own separate membership processes and privacy policies. We do not control sites that are operated by others and are not responsible for the information practices of these sites. Other sites may set their own cookies, collect data or solicit personal information. It is always a good idea to check the privacy policy and terms of use of any site before offering any of your Personal Information. We do not share your Personal Information with these independent web sites, except as noted above.

**Information Storage and Security**

Your Personal Information is stored on PIE computer servers (or those of its service providers. We protect your Personal Information with technical, administrative and physical safeguards to protect against loss, unauthorized access, destruction, misuse, modification and improper disclosure. No computer system or information can ever be fully protected against every possible hazard. But PIE is committed to providing reasonable and appropriate security controls to protect our PIE Sites and all Personal Information against foreseeable hazards.

Notwithstanding these security measures, please be aware that when you submit Personal Information to the PIE Sites over the Internet, the information may travel over many systems that are not under the PIE's control. We take the protection of user data very seriously and to that end take reasonable safeguards to prevent interception of any Personal Information. In the case of shopping pages, for example, the credit card information you submit is protected by secure servers.

**Accessing, Correcting and Updating Your Information**

To access, correct or update your account or other Personal Information such as your city or interests, please use the "Edit profile page" at the PIE Site on which you are registered.

If you have any other questions, comments or complaints about this policy, please contact us via our online forums or write to us at:

**Global Gaming League**  
**A Division of Professional Interactive Entertainment Inc.**  
Attn: Privacy Officer  
1524 Cloverfield Blvd., Suite E  
Santa Monica, CA 90404

*Be sure to include the specific PIE Site to which you are a member.

**Unsubscribe**

**Newsletters:** You may unsubscribe to email newsletters by following the instructions at the bottom of each newsletter or in your personal member profile

**Email updates and special offers:** You may unsubscribe to email announcements by following the instructions at the bottom of each email or using the opt-out features in your personal member profile.

**Services:** You may unsubscribe to any service for which you have previously elected by using the opt-out features in your personal member profile.

**Disputes:** In the case of disputes relating to complaints about PIE's privacy policy, PIE has chosen the American Arbitration Association as a mediator when it becomes evident that it will need an independent mediator to reach a mutual agreement between the two parties.

Effective 2/1/2006
